https://www.constablevat.com/privacy-policy/

View By ServiceVAT PlanningStrategically organise your business or charity to reduce your VAT liabilities.View ServiceVAT ReviewsHelp ensure compliance with an overall review of your VAT procedures.View ServiceDispute Prevention and ResolutionDisagreement with HMRC? Constable VAT can assist in putting your best case forward.View ServiceNon-Statutory ClearancesIf the law is unclear in how it applies to your situation, a non-statutory clearance can provide certainty.View ServiceVAT Risk ManagementIdentify any VAT risks to your business and take steps as early as possible to avoid them.View ServiceIn House VAT SupportNeed a new VAT person? Constable VAT can assist whilst you search and even help assess new candidates for you.View ServiceStaff VAT TrainingFrom the basics to the finer points, Constable VAT can tailor the right training for you and your team.View ServiceBrexit VAT PlanningAny questions about Brexit and the potential impact on your business?View ServiceView By SectorLand & PropertyEnsure that transactions involving land and buildings are treated correctly for VAT.View SectorDIY House Builder VAT ClaimsBuilding your dream home? Find out how to recover the VAT on costs.View SectorVAT & CharitiesIt can often be difficult to decide if an activity is business or non-business, particularly in the case of a charity. Constable VAT has sector specialists to assist charities.View SectorVAT, Insurance & FinanceThe insurance sector presents complex and unique VAT issues, especially around the recovery of input tax. Constable VAT has a lot of experience in this area of the law and can help to maximise input tax recovery.View SectorVAT & International ServicesMaking supplies overseas? Make sure that you are accounting for VAT properly on international transactions.View SectorAccountants & SolicitorsDoes your client have a complex VAT issue? Seek certainty from Constable VAT.View SectorYachtsYacht owners face many VAT issues when moving around the EU as they encounter the regimes of multiple Member States…View SectorAbout Our FirmAbout Constable VATConstable VAT is one of the largest independent specialist VAT firms in the UKView About UsEngaging Constable VATInterested in instructing Constable VAT to act for your business? Check the process…View Engaging Constable VATOur TeamTake a look at the members of the team at Constable VAT, see our credentials and our faces!View Our TeamCareersInterested in working with Constable VAT? Check out our current opportunitiesView CareersTestimonialsWe aim to provide a high level of service. You can leave feedback or read testimonials from our clients here.See Our TestimonialsCovid-19 VAT UpdatesMaking Tax Digital & VATBrexit & VATView By ServiceVAT PlanningVAT ReviewsDispute Prevention and ResolutionNon-Statutory ClearancesVAT Risk ManagementIn House VAT SupportStaff VAT TrainingBrexit VAT PlanningView By SectorLand & PropertyDIY House Builder VAT ClaimsVAT & CharitiesVAT, Insurance & FinanceVAT & International ServicesAccountants & SolicitorsYachtsAbout Our FirmAbout UsEngaging Our ServicesOur TeamCareersFAQ’sCovid-19 VAT UpdatesMaking Tax Digital & VATBrexit & VATDCase StudiesNewsContactSpeak To A Tax ExpertLT
Our CompanyTerms & conditionsPrivacyCookiesDisclaimerAdvice and money saving tips for your businessNews articles written by industry experts to help solve your VAT issues.Read Our NewsPrivacy PolicyThis privacy policy sets out how Constable VAT uses and protects any information that you give Constable VAT when you use this website.Constable VAT is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.Constable VAT may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 11 November 2013.What we collectWe may collect the following information:name and job titlecontact information including email addressWhat we do with the information we gatherWe require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:Internal record keeping.We may use the information to improve our products and services.We may periodically send emails about VAT issues, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.SecurityWe are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.Links to other websitesOur website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.Controlling your personal informationWe will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to Constable VAT Consultancy LLP, 12, Dedham Vale Business Centre, Manningtree Road, Dedham, Colchester CO7 6BL.If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect. Speak to our team of VAT experts Enquire Today
